// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What are two types of network layer firewalls?",
    answer: "Dynamic and static",
    options: [
      "Stateful",
      "stateless",
      "Dynamic and static",
      "Stateful and stateless"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following attacks requires a carrier file to self-replicate?",
    answer: "Trojan",
    options: [
      "Trojan",
      "Virus",
      "Worm",
      "Cascading"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Web page editors works on a ____ principle",
    answer: "WYSIWYG",
    options: [
      "WYSIWYG",
      "Hypertext Programming",
      "WWW",
      " WYGWYSI"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which program is used by web clients to view the web pages?",
    answer: "Web browser",
    options: [
      "Protocol",
      "Web server",
      "Search Engine",
      "Web browser"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is the name of the location address of the hypertext documents?",
    answer: "Web server",
    options: [
      "Web address",
      "File",
      "Uniform Resource Locator",
      "Web server"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What does XML stand for?",
    answer: "eXtensible Markup Language",
    options: [
      "eXtensible Markup Language",
      "eXecutable Multiple Language",
      "eXTra Multi-Program Language",
      "eXamine Multiple Language"
    ]
	
  },
  
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What are shared on the Internet and are called as Web pages?",
    answer: "Hypertext documents",
    options: [
      " None",
      "Hypertext documents",
      "Programs",
      "Cables"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "How many colour names are used by the browsers?",
    answer: "16",
    options: [
      "10",
      "16",
      "15",
      "20"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which tag is used to display text in title bar of a web document?",
    answer: "Title tag",
    options: [
      "Comment Tag",
      "Body tag",
      "Meta tag",
      "Title tag"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "The ____ attribute is used to identify the values of variables.",
    answer: "content",
    options: [
      "http-equiv",
      "text",
      "name",
      "content"
    ]
  },

  

  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];